Guide to the Mario Cardullo Papers, 1953-2013 MS2387
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Professional, 1957 June - 1988 August 26; 1957-1994; 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2
  - Yankee Noodle Dandy, 1983-1988; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 8
    - Rotary Cooking Apparatus Patent, 1986 July 01 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - The Atlantic "Pasta", 1986 July (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Yankee Noodle Trademark Patent, 1987 January 13 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Private Placement Memo Yankee Noodle Dandy, 1988 August 26 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - BMC Pastifico, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Caffe Panini, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Cardullos Pasta at Safeway, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Delish Restaurant, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Marketing Photos Yankee Noodle Dandy, undated (Box 17, Folders 15-16)
    - Noodle Production Photos + Negatives, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Record Book, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Restaurant Photos Yankee Noodle Dandy, undated (Box 18, Folders 3-6)
    - Selected Marketing Photos, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Suisse Italia Restaurant, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Restaurant, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Restaurant, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified Restaurant, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Pasta Shop, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Yankee Noodle Dandy Daily Diary, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Yankee Noodle Dandy Patches, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Restaurant Marketing Examples, undated (Flat box 22, Folder 5)
    - Strategic Plans, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ALS, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - C16, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Japanese Utility Company Procurment, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Belfield Group Inc., Alexandria, Virginia, 1994-1995; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9
    The folders in this sub-series are arranged chronologically.
    This sub-series contains documents, reports, publications, memos, correspondence, schematics and presentation materials. The materilas range from 1994-1995. This subseries relates to Cardullo's employment at the Belfeild Group Inc. in Alexandria, Virginia, where he served as Managing Director.
    - Belfield Group Inc.- Corporate Capabilities, 1994; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Preliminary Utility Procurment Practices Survey, 1994 June 23; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Prelimiary Report- Southwire Company, 1994 July 30; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Survey of Southwire Customers, 1994 August 25; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Final Report- Southwire Company [1/2], 1994 September 11; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Final Report- Southwire Company [2/2], 1994 September 19; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Priliminary Utility Procurment Procedures Survey, 1994 October 5-1994 November 22; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - USQS Trademark, 1995 March 13; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 9 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Patent Files, 2009-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10
    The folders in this subseries are arranged in order recieved by the donor.
    This sub-series contains documents, patent records, reserach notes, and correspondence. The material ranges from 2007-2013. Folders in this subseries relate to patents held by Cardullo, both in the United States and Europe.
    - Patent Files, 2008-2009; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Non-Disclosure Agreement, 2009; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Line Transformer 3035815-5000, 2008-2009; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - NANO RFID Method & Device [1/3], 2008-2010; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - NANO RFID Method & Device [2/3], 2010 January 26; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - NANO RFID Method & Device [3/3], 2011 June 30; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Method and System for Tracking [1/2], 2009 November 19; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Method and System for Tracking [1/2], 2009-2011; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Transmission of Electricity 2035815-5004PR, 2009-2011; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Distributed FRID Computer System 2035815-5005, 2009-2011; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - UV Generated Visable Light Source 20358-15-5006/5009, 2008-2011; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - UV Generated Visable Light Source II 20358-15-5006/5009, 2008-2011; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - UV Generated Visable LIght Source A, 2008-2011; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - UV Generated Visable LIght Source B, 2008-2011; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Patent Papers [1/4], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Patent Papers [2/4], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Patent Papers [3/4], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Patent Papers [4/4], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Bio-Detection & Pharmalogical Release 2035815-5014PR, 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - RFID & Chromosome Detection 2035815-5013PR, 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Credit Card User Protection 2035815-5011, 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Road Heating Device 2035815-5010 [1/2], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Road Heating Device 2035815-5010 [2/2], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Dynamically Triggerable Nano RFID [2035815-5008 [1/2], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Dynamically Triggerable Nano RFID 2035815-5008 [2/2], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Dynamically Distributable Nano RFID 2035815-5007 [1/2], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Dynamically Distributable Nano RFID 2035815-5008 [2/2], 2007-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 10 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 1964-2001; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11
    Folders in this subseries are arranded in order received by the donor.
    This sub-series contains documents, reports and publications. The materials range from 1963-2001, but are primarily undated. The folders in this subseries relates to publications written or co-written by Mario Cardullo, including publications on the Catholic Church and Electric Vechicles.
    - Systems Approach to Catholic Church, 1964; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Catholic Population of Great Falls, 1964; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - @Risk Paper, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - AMT Paper, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - CATV Project, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Hondoras Project, 1973 October 5; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Impact of Technology on Employment, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - IT Book, 2001; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Matla Project, 1983; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Published Books, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Real Estate Models, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 11 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Files, 1983-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12
    This sub-series contains documents, patent records, buisness plans, reserach notes, presentation materials, reports, and correspondence. The materials range from 1983-2012, but are primarily undated. Records in this subseries relate to Mario Cardullo's buisness and scientific career.
    - Tracking, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - RFID Original, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - NANO RFID, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - RFID Other, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Total Life Cycle Cost Model for Electric Power, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - TLCC Power Standards, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - TLCC Model Vechicles, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - TLCC Model Electric Vechicles, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Super English World, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - UV Light, 2013; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - European Patent Records, 2009-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - NR LLC, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Archimedes [1/2], undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Archimedes [2/2], undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Arctrak, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Arichmedes Corporation, undated; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Patents- Other, 2009-2012; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Life Cycle Cost Analysis of Conventional and Fuel Cell/Battery Powered Urban Passanger Vechicles, 1992 November 30; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Total Life Cycle Cost Model for Electric Power Station, 1995 January; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Impact of Internet on North American Automobile Industry [1/2], 2000 September 14; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Impact of Internet on North American Automobile Industry [2/2], 2000 October 12; MS2387 Series 2 Subseries 12 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Personal and Office Records, 1956-2005; MS2387 Series 3
  This series contains documents, publications, notes, memos, correspondence, record books, photos, negatives, and slides that relate to Mario Cardullos personal life and personal office records. The material ranges from 1956-2005.
  - Personal Photos, 1956-1958 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Wedding June 1958, Pam 1st Nov '60, 1958 June -1960 November (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Note from "W.W.", 1959 November 23 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - America Article, 1967 November 11 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Paul Backyard, Cub Scout Picnic, Mexico I, 1971 June (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Venture Management Corporation Mexican Exports, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cooking Instructions, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Desk Diary, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Commercial Real Estate Finance Course, 1989 December (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - RFID An Educational Primer, 2000 January 19 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The history of RFID, 2001 October 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Capital Formation in Central America, 2003 March 18 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Anatomy of RFID Technology Dr. Tom Mierzwa, 2004 March 17 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Mercury News Correspondence, 2004 June 08 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Credibility, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Lemelson-MIT Prize, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Party, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Construction Site, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Misc, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Publications and Resume, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - RFID Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - RFID Patent, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)